I ate seven pints of ice cream this week
and was still able to maintain a caloric
deficit. This is all thanks to the Ninja
Swirl, the brand new version of the
Ninja Creamy that just launched last
week. Let me show you all the different
flavors I made this week. That first one
you saw was me trying out a new vanilla
base recipe. It was phenomenal. Then the
next day, I adjusted it into a cake
batter recipe, which was even better.
Then I switched it up a little. I did a
salted caramel Oreo, which was one of my
favorite flavors I've ever made. And
then for Valentine's Day, I did a red
velvet flavor. You guys might have seen
this recipe on my page. It is so so
good. And then my friends wanted to try
the new Ninja Swirl. So, I got
absolutely mobile with the Ninja Swirl.
I packed it up in a suitcase and brought
it over. And I let them request whatever
flavors they wanted. So, they wanted the
double Oreo that I literally just made
and then the red velvet. And I think
it's safe to say that everyone loved it.
They couldn't believe that it was low
calorie and high protein.
>> Wow, that's pretty good. And then I
ended off the week with this
twoingredient strawberry banana ice
cream, which was so thick and so so